alexage.com 2013-06-06

# Increase Alexa Rank | Improve Alexa Ranking | Boost Alexa Rank | Privacy Policy

Rankage has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy to our customers and users of this website. This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Rankage uses, maintains and discloses information collected from its customers and users of its website.

## Privacy

Rankage is committed to developing long-lasting relationships based on trust. In furtherance of this goal, Rankage will do everything in its power to ensure that your right to privacy is maintained and protected. This website is not directed at children under 13 years of age.

## Information We Collect

Rankage may request or collect information from online users, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where users are invited to volunteer such information.

The only data we collect is the following information that identifies you, such as:

  * Your name
  * E-mail address
  * Website URL

Rankage may also collect information about how users access the website using a tracking ID unique to each user through the use of cookies.

## What are Cookies?

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We may use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For session ID cookies, once you close your browser or log out, the cookie terminates and is erased. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on your computer’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Your browser’s help file contains information and instructions for removing persistent cookies. Session ID cookies may be used by Rankage to track user preferences while the user is visiting the website. They also help to minimize load times and save on server processing..

## Log Files

Like most standard websites, we use log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. However, none of the information stored in our log files, including but not limited to IP addresses, is linked to personally identifiable information.

## How we use this information

Rankage may use the personally identifiable information collected by Rankage to contact customers regarding products and services offered by Rankage. We may also use this information for research purposes regarding the effectiveness of our website services, marketing, advertising and sales efforts. Rankage will not in any way share this information with a third party either for free or by selling it.

## Special Offers and Updates

Our customers and users will occasionally receive newsletters or e-mails with information on products, services, or special offers. Out of respect for the privacy of our users, Rankage gives them the opportunity to opt-out from receiving these types of communications.

## Service Announcements

On rare occasions, it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement, if, for instance, our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications, though they can deactivate their account. However, these communications are not promotional in nature.

## Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve your privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law, if we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary and required to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order, subpoena or other legal process served on Rankage.

The Rankage website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Rankage is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The Rankage Privacy Policy as described herein applies solely to information collected by Rankage.

## Maintenance of Information

The information provided to Rankage is saved indefinitely and may be stored on one or more databases directly or indirectly maintained by Rankage. Rankage employs industry-standard security measures to protect the confidentiality of the information.
